

EDCIL JONAS PENASO (415) 350-7517 San Francisco, CA edciljonas15@yahoo.com

Profile

A Culinary Professional with 8 years of experience running high level culinary teams.

Passionate about proficiency and attention to detail.

I am self taught Web Developer and am now seeking for opportunities in tech related to Software Development where I can showcase and enhance my skills and be surrounded by like minded individuals to share and learn new skills and ideas.

Tech Stacks

- HTML & CSS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- React.js
- Express
- Node.js
- SQL
- Mongoose
- MongoDB
- Heroku
- Git
- Github

<u>Portfolio</u>

https://jp-react-portfolio.herokuapp.com/

EDUCATION

Complete Web Development Bootcamp 2021 by Dr. Angela Yu **Udemy**

Modern HTML & CSS(Including SASS) 2021 by Brad Traversy **Udemy**

Degree in Culinary Arts - 2011

MOST Institute Culinary School, Islacare Inc., Davao, Philippines

EXPERIENCE

Flagship Facility Services @ Facebook | San Francisco | California Jr. Sous Chef | 2019 - Current

Responsibilities:

• Oversee day to day operations and mentoring team members and support their needs.

Flagship Facility Services @ Facebook | San Francisco | California Line Cook, Lead Line Cook | 2018-2019

Responsibilities:

· Menu plan and execute task given.

Birdsong | San Francisco | California Chef de Partie, Tournant | 2018

Responsibilities:

- Execute daily changing menu.
- R&D

Gibson | San Francisco, California Chef de Partie, Tournant | 2017-2018

Responsibilities:

 Executing recipes in accordance to the Chefs direction. Assist team members during operation.

In Situ | San Francisco ,California Chef de Partie, Commis, Kitchen Runner, Kitchen Server | 2016- 2017

Responsibilities:

- Execute given task and ensure product quality from start to finish.
- · Assist guests when needed.

Selland's Market Café | East Sacramento, California Line Cook | 2014-2016

Responsibilities:

Execute given task.

Marco Polo Hotel | Davao, Philippines Apprentice Chef | 2011

Responsibilities:

- Assist different kitchen stations and ensure product quality.
- Completed required internship time.

Certificates:

- Complete Web Development Bootcamp 2021
- Modern HTML & CSS(Including SASS) 2021
- California Food Handler Card
- National Certificate in Commercial Cooking II
- Technical Education and Skills Development Authority (TESDA)
- Certificate of Training Marco Polo Hotel
- Certificate of Training in Commercial Cooking II MOST Institute Culinary School, Islacare Inc.